so you need to divide a circular Pizza
seven equal ways and all you have is a
straight edge Encompass no worries I've
got you covered first take the diameter
of the pizza and cut it into seven equal
pieces which you can do with a straight
edge Encompass now use your compass to
draw these seven semi-circles you should
have one semi-circle of diameter ND for
each value of n from one up to seven
like this
now here's the trick you want to do the
exact same construction on the bottom
half of the pizza except this time from
right to left
these are the resulting seven pieces
that you have and they're all equal in
area if you want to know more about why
this works check out the link in the
description to the longer video
describing all the details